consumertrack.com 2018-08-22

# ConsumerTrack - Privacy Policy

ConsumerTrack™ Inc owns and operates thousands of consumers Websites and portions of other Web pages and Web content through which you have accessed this Privacy Policy (collectively, “WEBSITES”). By visiting, using and/or submitting information to WEBSITES, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions of WEBSITE’s Agreement of Terms of Use.

ConsumerTrack™, Inc. and our affiliated companies worldwide (“ConsumerTrack™”) are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us. ConsumerTrack™ has established this Online PRIVACY POLICY so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information. In general, you can visit ConsumerTrack™’s Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the Web, we may transfer that Information within ConsumerTrack™ or to ConsumerTrack™’s third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.

ConsumerTrack™ strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, ConsumerTrack™ intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online PRIVACY POLICY even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about website activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the website. If you prefer that your browser does not store this cookie information, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to “opt out” of the benefits of cookies, you can manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the “Help” section of your browser. Alternatively, simply click the “OPT OUT NOW” link provided, below. ConsumerTrack™ uses a limited number of third party providers to manage cookies, and when you click the link below, you will be opted out of their tracking systems. Note that separate browser windows will be opened, and you need to allow pop-ups for this to happen. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to ConsumerTrack™. The notice we intend to provide where ConsumerTrack™ collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of ConsumerTrack™’s websites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

If you chose to have a relationship with ConsumerTrack™, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.

If you no longer wish to receive communications via email, you may opt-out emailing info@consumertrack.com or sending written correspondence to 2121 Rosecrans Ave, Ste 1300, Los Angeles, CA 90245. To have your personal information completely removed from our databases, simply contact us at privacy@consumertrack.com and provide the name of the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, phone number and email address so that we may identify you in the opt-out process. Once we receive your instruction, we will promptly take corrective action.

## Security

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within ConsumerTrack™ or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

## Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, ConsumerTrack™ wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting ConsumerTrack™ should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to privacy@consumertrack.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.

## Children’s Privacy

ConsumerTrack™.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age.

## Commitment

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and ConsumerTrack™’s websites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online PRIVACY POLICY, please contact us at privacy@consumertrack.com. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

## Your Consent

By using this website, you consent to the terms of our Online PRIVACY POLICY and to ConsumerTrack™’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where ConsumerTrack™ collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online PRIVACY POLICY change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our website for a reasonable period of time.

## Contacting Us

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding ConsumerTrack™’s Privacy Policy, you may email us at privacy@consumertrack.com or you can send correspondence to the following address:

## Governing Law; Arbitration

You agree that: (i) www.CONSUMERTRACK.com shall be deemed solely based in the State of California; and (ii) www.CONSUMERTRACK.com shall be deemed a passive Web site that does not give rise to personal jurisdiction over CONSUMERTRACK, either specific or general, in jurisdictions other than the State of California. This Privacy Policy is to be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of California, without regard for principles of conflicts of laws. Any civil action, claim, dispute or proceeding arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy shall be referred to final and binding arbitration, before a single arbitrator, under the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association in Los Angeles County, California.

THEREFORE, YOU DO NOT HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO GO TO COURT TO ASSERT OR DEFEND YOUR RIGHTS AND YOU GIVE UP YOUR RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN OR BRING CLASS ACTIONS. BY USING WWW.CONSUMERTRACK.COM YOU CONSENT TO THESE RESTRICTIONS. You and CONSUMERTRACK shall select the arbitrator, and if you and CONSUMERTRACK are unable to reach agreement on selection of the arbitrator within thirty (30) days after the notice of arbitration is served, then the American Arbitration Association shall select the arbitrator. Arbitration shall not commence until the party requesting it has deposited One Thousand Dollars ($1,000.00) with the arbitrator for the arbitrator’s fees and costs. The party requesting arbitration shall advance such sums as are required from time to time by the arbitrator to pay the arbitrator’s fees and costs until the prevailing party is determined or the parties have agreed in writing to an alternate allocation of fees and costs.

Judgment upon any award rendered by the arbitrator shall be final, binding and conclusive upon you and CONSUMERTRACK and your and CONSUMERTRACK’s respective administrators, executors, legal representatives, successors and assigns, and may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction. Notwithstanding the previous sentence, in no event shall either you or CONSUMERTRACK be entitled to punitive, special, indirect or consequential damages and both you and CONSUMERTRACK hereby waive your and CONSUMERTRACK’s respective rights to any punitive, special, indirect or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, damages for any loss of profit, revenue or business.

Should a dispute arise and should the arbitration provisions herein become inapplicable or unenforceable, or in any instance of any lawsuit between you and CONSUMERTRACK, jurisdiction over and venue of any suit shall be exclusively in the state and federal courts sitting in Los Angeles County, California.

## Miscellaneous

If any portion of this Privacy Policy is deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable by any arbitrator, this Privacy Policy as a whole shall not be deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable, but only that portion of this Privacy Policy that is unlawful, void or unenforceable shall be stricken from this Privacy Policy. The headings contained in this Privacy Policy are for convenience of reference only, are not to be considered a part of this Privacy Policy, and shall not limit or otherwise affect in any way the meaning or interpretation of this Privacy Policy.

All covenants, agreements, representations and warranties made in this Privacy Policy, as may be amended by CONSUMERTRACK from time to time, shall survive your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@consumertrack.com](mailto:info@consumertrack.com).
